Guide to the Stanford University, Feminist Studies Program, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Feminist Studies Program, records
1980-1998
SC0673
Stanford University. Feminist Studies Program.
18.5 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Materials were acquired by administrative transfer, 2002.
Information about Access
Access: Collection is partially restricted; please consult the University Archivist for access.
Scope and Contents note
Records include administrative files, financial records, syllabi, curriculum files, course evaluations, and files on students.
Access Terms
Feminist theory--Study and teaching (Higher).; Women's studies.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH.2002-304
  - Course Proposals, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Women's Studies Course Lists/Workshops @ other school (part 2), 1970-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - GER Application for FS101, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Five Year Self-Study Info, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Women Studies Course Lists/Workshops @ other schools, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Individually Designed Major, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Individually Designed Major Worksheet (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sample Major Proposals, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Co-terminal Degrees, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - FS Course Poster, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - FS Course Poster, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - FS Course Poster, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - FS Poster, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Autumn Courses, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Winter Courses, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Summer Courses, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Spring Courses, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Autumn Courses, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Winter Courses, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Spring Courses, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Summer Courses, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Summer Courses, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Winter Classes, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Autumn Courses, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Course Proposals, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Course Proposals, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Course Proposals, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Distribution Requirements, 1985-1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Distribution & Gender Studies Requirements, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Outside Course Proposals, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Graduate Student Course Proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Graduate Student Course Proposals, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Graduate Student Course Proposals, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Graduate Student Course Proposals, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Graduate Student Course Proposals, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Graduate Student Course Proposals, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Practicum Ideas, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Sample Undergraduate Special Course Proposal, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Directed Reading Forms, 1900s (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Syllabi, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Class Lists and extras, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Spring Courses, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Summer Courses, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Courses & Degrees, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Course Information, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Course Info. & Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Course Info & Misc., 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Curriculum Development, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Curriculum, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Curriculum, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Curriculum, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Courses & Degrees, 1987-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Autumn Syllabi, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Winter Syllabi, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Spring Syllabi, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Spring Syllabi, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Winter Syllabi, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Fall Courses, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Spring Syllabi, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Winter Syllabi, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Fall Syllabi, 1984-1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Winter Syllabi, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Spring Syllabi, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Spring Syllabi, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Winter Syllabi, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Fall Syllabi, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Spring, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fall Syllabi, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Spring Syllabi, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Autumn Syllabi, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Winter Syllabi, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Spring Syllabi, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Autumn Syllabi, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Winter Syllabi, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Spring Syllabi, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Spring Syllabi, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Winter Syllabi, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Autumn Syllabi, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Spring Syllabi, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Winter Syllabi, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Autumn Syllabi, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Draft for Courses & Degrees, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Courses & Degrees, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Coruses & Degrees, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Courses Supported by FS, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Faculty Courses Proposals (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Possible Courses, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Future Courses, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Graduate Student Course Proposals, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - FS Spanish Conversation Course, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - FS, WIM, TA training info., 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - FS Curriculum, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Winter Quarter, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Curriculum Feedback from Resource Faculty, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Spring Quarter, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Autumn Quarter Time Schedule, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - FS Program Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Curriculum, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Spring Quarter, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - FS Poster, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Graduate Student Courses, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Faculty Course Development Proposals, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Graduate Student Course Proposals, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - ASSU Course Guide, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Autumn/Spring Course Evaluations, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Survey of Courses (Autumn), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Survey Of Courses (Winter), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Survey of Courses, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Survey of Courses (Autumn), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Course Evaluations (Spring), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Course Evaluations (Autumn), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Course Evaluations (Autumn), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Course Evaluations (Spring), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Course Evaluations (Spring), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Course Evaluations (Winter), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Course Evaluations (Spring), 1986 (Box 3)
  - Course Evaluations (Winter, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Course Evaluations (Autumn), 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Course Evaluations (Autumn), 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Course Evaluations (Spring), 1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Course Evaluations (Winter), 1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Course Evaluations (Winter), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Autumn (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Autumn (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Course Evaluations (Autumn), 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Course Evaluations (Autumn), 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Course Evaluation (Spring) (1of 2), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Course Evaluation Spring (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Course Evaluations (Spring), 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Course Evaluations (Winter), 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Course Evaluations (winter), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Course Evaluation (Spring), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Course Evaluations, Autumn (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Course Evaluations, Autumn (2 of 3), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Course Evaluations, Autumn (3 of 3), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Course Evaluations, Autumn, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Course Evaluations, Spring (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Course Evaluations, Spring 1991 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Course Evaluations, Winter, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Course Evaluation, 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Course Evaluations, Autumn, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence & Curriculum Vitaes, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Junior Convocation, Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Alumni Donation Transmittal, Corr. & Article, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Gay & Lesbian Studies, Corr. & Fin., 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Grad Student Focus Group, Correspondence, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Resource Faculty, Corr. & Matierals, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Juniors' Lunch-Corr., 1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Mailing Lists, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - E-Mail Lists, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Old Mailing Labels, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Corr. w/ other Programs, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Corr.--Inquiries about Program., 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Inquires about Program (not able to give info. requested), 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Inquiries about Program, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Mailing Lists, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Mailing Lists, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Mailing Lists, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Mailing Lists, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Mailing Lists, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Mailing Lists, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Mailing Lists, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Mailing Lists & Corr., 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - General Memos (in & out), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - General Memos, (in & out), 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - General Corr., 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - General Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - General Corr., 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Stanford Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - General Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Courses and Majors, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Corr. w/ Majors, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Corr. w/ Major 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - State of the Program Memo, 1987 Oct (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - FS Committee Corr., 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - FS Committee Corr., 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - FS Committee Corr., 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - CHRON File, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - CHRON File, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Inquiries about Program, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Inquiries about Program, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Inquiries about Program, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Inquiries about Program, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Letter from FS Faculty, RE: Humanities Ctr. Director, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Faculty Seminar Readings (1 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Faculty Seminar Readings (2 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Faculty Seminar Readings (3 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Faculty Seminar in Feminist Theory, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Faculty Seminar in Feminist Theory, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Faculty Seminar, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Faculty Seminar in Feminist Theory, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Faculty Seminar in Feminist Theory, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - FS Seminar--Syllabus, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Rollo May Seminar, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - FS Faculty Seminar--request for summer funds, 1984 May (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Research Seminar, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Research Seminar, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Research Seminar, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Research Seminar, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Seminar in Feminist Theory, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Seminar in Feminist Theory, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Seminar in Feminist Theory (1 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Seminar in Feminist Theory (2 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Seminar in Feminist Thoery, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meeting, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Pedagogy Lunch (FS/CSRE), 1990-1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Seminar, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - DAST (newsletter) Advisory Committee, Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Tips Working Group Meeting, 1994 Oct (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Student Members of Program Committee, Resumes & Correspondence, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Student Members of Program Committee, Timelines (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Program Committe, Undergraduate rep. Search, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Program committee, Graduate Rep. Search, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - FS Committee Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - FS Committee Meeting Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - FS Committee Meeting Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - FS Committee Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Feminist Studies Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - FS Committee Material, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - FS Committee Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - FS Committee Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Undergraduate applications for FS Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - FS Committee Correspondence, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - FS Committee Undergraduate Applications, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - FS Committee Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - FS Committee Undergraduate Applications, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Student Applications for Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Quarterly Info. Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Information Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Information Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - FS Program Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - FS Quarterly Planning Agenda, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Status of Women Faculty Senate, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - FS Committee Student Applications, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - International Students (FS Committee), 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Interested Students (FS CommitteE), 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Apps for FS Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Stanford Bookstore, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Budget, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Budget & Seminar, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Budget & Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Major Advising Enhancement Program, Proposal, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Faculty Senate, Degree Requirements & Modified Seaver Proposals, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Center for Teaching & Learning, liason material, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Work Study Information, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Programs of Campus, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Interviewing Procedures, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Staff Training Notes, 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Awards File, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Newsletter/Articles, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Administration, Financial, Courses, Circa 1994 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Women & Scientific Literary Grants, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Visitng Scholar Roshni Rustomji's talk, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Books Info, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Humanities & Social Science Initiatives, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Retirement, Employment, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - National Women's Studies Association (NWSA), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Brown Bag Series, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Newspaper Articles/Clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Film Info, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Global Fund for Women, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Internships, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Newsletter & General Info on major/minor/course, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Lectures and Miscellaneous Into, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Speakers/Films, 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Exchange Programs, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Essays on Gender, Feminisms, & the Media, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Sexual Assault Legal Advocay Program, Request for Tunnel, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Harvard Women's Studies, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - 1983, Bardnard Women's Center (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - UC Berkeley Report on Women's Studies, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Practicum, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Ruth Doell, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Pamela Eakins, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Marcia Falk, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Barbara Freeman, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Rose Glickman, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Program Review 2, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Program Review, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Program News, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Account of FS Program, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Account of FS PRogram, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Account of FS Program, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Feminist Film Theory, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Resource Faculty Resumes (Originals), 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Updated Faculty Resumes, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Resource Faculty Resume Book, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - FS/Gender Focus House, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Rape Crisis Hotline Volunteer, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Women's History Week, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Women's History Month, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Women's History Week, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Commencement & Diploma Awards, 1986 Jun (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Graduation Party, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Reception for new Women Faculty, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Reception for New Women Faculty, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Reception for New Women Faculty, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Reception for New Women Faculty, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Reception for New Women Faculty, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - International Women's Day, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Sponsored Speakers and Events, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Sponsored Speakers & events, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Sponsored Speakers & Events, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Sponsored Speakers & Events, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Sponsored Speakers & Events, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Sponsored Speakers & Events, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Sponsored Speakers and Events, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Sponsored Speakes & Events, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Sponsored Speakers & Events, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Fall Registration Info, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - FS Events, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Women Making Music, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - The Legal Meaning of Equality, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Sponsored Projects/Events, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - FS Program Suggestions, fantasies, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Enrollment Figures, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Enrollment Figures, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Course Enrollment, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Course Enrollment Data, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Senior Survey, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Women's Studies Core Faculty Retreat, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Sponsored Speakers & Events, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Sponsored Speakers & Events, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Sponsored Speakers & Events, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - GWN Conferene: The Feminist University, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Women's Humor and Social Satire, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Feminist Publishing Reception, 1987 Mar (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - FS101: Women's Situation, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Application for FS Support, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Take Our Daughters, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Take Your Daughters to Work Day, 1998 Apr (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Ford Grant, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Comp. Persp. on Race, Ethnicity, Gender, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - FS/CSRE/IRWG Ford Proposal, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Alternative Spring Break, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - New Women Faculty Reception, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - New Women Faculty Reception, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Commencement, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Open House, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Student Salary Rates, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Capestone/Gateway Proposal, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Property Administration, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Space Inventory, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Stuart Rental Company Promotional Packet (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - FS Matierlas on Film/Video, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - FS Matierals on Micro/Video (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - FS Events, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Feminist Film Series Catalogues & coursehandouts, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Women's Studies Programs - Western (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - FS Sponsored Programs, 1983 Aug (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Library Wish-List, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Women's Studies Programs - Overseas (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Fellowships for Graduates (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Toward a graduate program in FS. Correspondence Minutes (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Toward a Graduate Program in FS, Women's Studies Materials (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Fellowships/Scholarships, 1985-1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Publications Available, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Books, Miscellaneous, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Ford Foundation, 1980 Sep (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Graduate Women's Studies Programs (Eastern), Circa 1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Graduate Women's Studies Programs (California), 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Daily Ads, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - FS Commencement, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - List of Programs, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Jobs & Programs for FS Majors, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Business Meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - FS Core Faculty, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Stanford Women's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Funding Requests, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - FS Speakers, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Computers, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - FS Advising, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - End of Year Party, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - FS Open house, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Undergraduate Women Studies - East coast, Circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Misc., 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Faculty Club, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - IRWG Conference Room, Circa 1997 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Pulse Copy Claim Checks, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Enrollment Info, 1990-1995 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Undergraduate Women's Studies Programs - West Coast (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Undergraduate Women's Studies Schools. Mid-West, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Undergraduate Women Studies, South and Overseas, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Undergraduate Women Studies Programs, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Administrative Serries, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - SUFIN, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - 1990 Jul (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Jane Collier, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Regenia Gagnier, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Estelle Freedman, 1987 Apr (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Elisabeth Hansot, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Margo Horn, 1985-1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Anne Mellor, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)